6695 TRIGO ROAD ISLA VISTA, CA 93117 (626) 529-4008 MATHEWKRAMSCH@GMAIL.COM

MATHEW KRAMSCH

About Me

I am a 4th year UCSB Computer Science student interested in all software development but specifically web and mobile development. With experience in both front-end and back-end languages I can operate as a Full-Stack developer, and my background in visual arts ties into my passion for user interface design.

Software Development

```
Programming Languages: C++, Java, some Python, Javascript, HTML, CSS
Frameworks: Next.js, Node.js
Tools: Git, Github, NPM, Linux (Ubuntu, Fedora, Manjaro)
Skills:
```

- * strong knowledge of object-oriented programming, Agile, and Test Driven Development
- * experience in developing static websites and full scale web applications
- \star Team Programming, server management, and database management

Education

```
University of California, Santa Barbara — Computer Science
Senior - Class of 2021, GPA: 3.61
```

Work Experience

```
Hope Refuge, Goleta — Sous-Chef
```

MARCH 2019 - CURRENT

Worked as a cook for a newly opened non-profit residential therapeutic and rehabilitative program for teenagers

- Cooked lunch and dinner for the 25+ people living at the camp
- Did food preparation, washed dishes, maintained the kitchen
- Helped plan out meals and write menus

UC Police Department, UC Santa Barbara - Community Service Officer

SEPTEMBER 2019 - MARCH 2020

Was a part of a professional unit of the Police Department, acting as a liaison between the UCSB student body and UCPD. Provided safety and security for students, staff, and faculty on the UCSB campus and within Isla Vista.

- Patrolled UCSB campus and housing reporting crimes in progress and assisting in emergency situations
- Responded to various high-pressure situations such as traffic collisions and alcohol/drug overdoses in a professional and authoritative manner
- Did crowd control and security for on-campus events and concerts
- Communicated with UCPD dispatch via radio

Domino's Pizza, Isla Vista - In-store Worker

APRIL 2019 - JUNE 2019

Worked as an in-store worker, making pizzas, working the cash register, and providing customer service

- Took orders and used the cash register to check out customers
- Worked in the kitchen making pizzas, prepping toppings, and taking pizzas out of the oven
- Washed dishes, swept, mopped, and cleaned the store
- Provided customer service and resolved issues

Cold Stone Creamery, Goleta - Shift Lead

AUGUST 2018 - NOVEMBER 2018

Ran work shifts at a busy ice cream shop, preparing, making, and serving ice cream "creations"

- Handled customer service requests and resolved issues
- Determined employee roles during shifts
- Was responsible for closing down and locking the store
- Used the cash register to check out customers
- Mixed toppings into ice cream, and made shakes, smoothies, and frappés
- Washed dishes, swept, mopped, and cleaned the store

Kmart, Goleta - Cashier Associate

AUGUST 2018 - SEPTEMBER 2018

Worked temporarily at a going-out-of-business department store, operating the cash register and assisting customers

- Used the cash register to check out customers
- Assisted in loss prevention by checking receipts as customers exited the store
- Greeted customers and assisted them in finding items
- Operated pallet jacks to help receive and distribute shipments throughout the store

Portola Dining Commons, Isla Vista - Student Worker

OCTOBER 2017 - APRIL 2018

Worked in a UCSB Residence Hall dining commons, serving food and working in the kitchen

- Served food to customers, kept the area presentable, and provided customer service
- Assisted cooks in preparing food
- Washed dishes, silverware, and pots/pans/kettles
- Was responsible for bussing and cleaning tables, sweeping, and mopping
- Helped clean up the dining commons after closing

Antigua Bread, Los Angeles – Waiter/Busser

JULY 2017 - SEPTEMBER 2017

Worked at a a classic spanish café/restaurant, serving food and bussing tables

- Served food to customers
- Assisted barista in preparing and making drinks
- Cleaned/bussed tables, helped maintain the presentation of the restaurant
- Washed dishes, silverware, and pots/pans

Postmates, Los Angeles — Food Delivery Courier

JUNE 2017 - SEPTEMBER 2017

Worked for an online delivery service as a delivery driver, delivering food and other goods to customers

- Provided top customer service with a high rating
- Received tips for fast delivery and exceeding customer expectations